In conclusion, there are three things you need to remember.
Firstly, there are five steps for table completions
and summary completion.
Remember to pay attention to the distractors.
For example, the sentence in the question is
in the passive voice, but in the recording
it is in the active voice.
This makes students miss the information even when
they've identified the key words.
Next, you should also focus on the use
of signposting language, such as however, but, apart
from, and except. After listening,
you should check your answers in terms of
spelling, grammatical structures, and meanings.
Another thing you should bear in mind is
that to gain high scores, you have to
understand what the speaker wants to convey.
Therefore, you should improve your vocabulary regularly.
Let's study hard guys, I hope you will achieve
your desired score.
For now, goodbye and see you in the next lesson.